logicalmedia.com 2010-12-19

# Affiliate Network / Make Money Online

Privacy Policy

COMPANY PRACTICES  
The following statement describes the overall company practices of LOGICAL MEDIA, including advertising on our network of websites, as well as across other internal sites, and products and services that are offered by LOGICAL MEDIA. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that LOGICAL MEDIA does not own or control, or to people that LOGICAL MEDIA does not employ.

INFORMATION COLLECTED BY LOGICAL MEDIA  
Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Data

LOGICAL MEDIA delivers advertisements across multiple channels and media, including to web surfers who visit any of the websites that are a part of LOGICAL MEDIA network. With respect to individuals who visit those sites, we collect anonymous information such as a web surfer's IP address, web pages which have been viewed by a web surfer, date and time, domain type, and responses by a web surfer to an advertisement delivered by us. We use different types of technologies to collect this type of information, including cookies and pixels.

Additionally, LOGICAL MEDIA occasionally runs promotions and sweepstakes offers through various Internet channels (collectively referred to as "LOGICAL MEDIA Properties"), and collects information at those sites. As a part of the registration process at the LOGICAL MEDIA Properties, we may request and collect additional non-personally identifiable information about the visitor. Examples of the non-personally identifiable data that may be requested include age, gender, and interests. None of the foregoing information (collectively referred to as "non-personally identifiable data"), by itself, or together, can by its nature be tracked to a specific individual. Individuals who have provided registration data may elect to have their data deleted from our files, or kept from being used for purposes other than for the service requested, by contacting LOGICAL MEDIA at privacy@LogicalMedia.com . Personally identifiable information that is collected at the LOGICAL MEDIA Properties is discussed immediately below.

Personally Identifiable Consumer Data  
At some of the LOGICAL MEDIA Properties, we ask people to register and provide personally identifiable data. LOGICAL MEDIA is committed to making sure that clear notice and choice is provided to all consumers before the personally identifiable data is collected, and that they have opted-in to our use of their data. Examples of personally identifiable data that may be requested include name, address, and email address. Individuals who have provided personally identifiable data may elect to have their data deleted from our files, or kept from being used for purposes other than for the service requested, by contacting LOGICAL MEDIA at privacy@LogicalMedia.com. Other Information that is Collected

At some LOGICAL MEDIA Properties, including this one, LOGICAL MEDIA collects personal information on individuals and companies who want to enter into business relationships with LOGICAL MEDIA ("business information"). An example of this would include web publishers who want to become a part of LOGICAL MEDIA web network. We maintain business information for purposes of administering the program, such as maintaining account information, sending payments, etc. We may share business information with third parties who provide administrative services (and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information), as well as pursuant to a court order or to law enforcement or government officials as we deem necessary or appropriate. How Collected Information is Used

The non-personally identifiable data that LOGICAL MEDIA collects is used for marketing and sales efforts to better target advertisements and other content to individuals in an effort to create a personally relevant experience for each person. The data is also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform best and which content is most appropriate for different individuals. If a consumer elects to provide LOGICAL MEDIA with personally identifiable data, we may utilize such data for marketing purposes. In addition, that data may be combined with information collected from other sources to assist with targeting ads to that consumer's preferences and behaviors, and for other LOGICAL MEDIA sales and marketing efforts. Sharing With Third Parties

All personally identifiable data provided by individuals is maintained in confidence by LOGICAL MEDIA. There are instances, however, in which personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information is shared with third parties, as described below. The non-personally identifiable data may be shared with third-party partners of LOGICAL MEDIA on an anonymous basis.

With respect to personally identifiable information, LOGICAL MEDIA may, from time to time, provide information to certain third-party administrative vendors for efficiency purposes in providing administrative services such as billing, delivery and pay-outs, or for other services related to providing a LOGICAL MEDIA product or service. Any third-party vendor so used will be required to enter into a confidentiality agreement with LOGICAL MEDIA.

LOGICAL MEDIA may also share personally identifiable information with third parties who enter into business relationships with us. These business partners may include financial service providers (including credit bureaus and insurance agents); non-financial companies (including retailers, online and offline advertisers, membership list vendors, direct marketers and publishers); companies that perform marketing services on our behalf, and others such as non-profit organizations. We may also disclose information to a third party who provides substantially similar services as the original service signed up for, if we decide to stop providing such services ourselves. In such situations, we will provide our subscribers with an opportunity to opt-out of such sharing. Please be aware that LOGICAL MEDIA is very careful about which companies it does business with. In addition to the above, there is also the possibility that LOGICAL MEDIA, or part(s) of the company, may one day be purchased by, or merged with, another company. If that's the case, the acquiring (or merging) company will have access to your information. Finally, LOGICAL MEDIA may share information on individuals as it deems necessary to comply with a court order or to cooperate with government and law enforcement officials.

Security Precautions  
LOGICAL MEDIA makes significant efforts to maintain the security of its network and the data we collect. We use various technologies, including, in certain instances, encryption, to ensure the high security standards. Any data that is stored on LOGICAL MEDIA servers is treated as confidential and is not generally available to the public. LOGICAL MEDIA has an internal security policy with respect to the confidentiality of customer and other data, limiting access only to those employees who we reasonably believe need to know such information for the purpose of performing their jobs. Please keep in mind, however, that the Internet is not a 100% secure medium. Therefore, although we use reasonable efforts to protect information, the possibility of somebody defeating our security measures does exist.

CONSUMER CHOICE  
Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Data - Use of Cookies & Opting-Out LOGICAL MEDIA uses technology, including cookies and pixels, to deliver better, targeted marketing messages to individuals. These tools are used to collect anonymous data, and in some instances where personally identifiable information has been provided by a user, to provide better and more relevant services and messages to that user. We believe that the use of such tools assists in providing a more meaningful web-surfing experience.

Personally Identifiable Consumer Data - Opt-Out  
If a consumer elects to provide LOGICAL MEDIA with personally identifiable data, he or she has the right to tell us not to make some of the uses of such data described herein or may have such data deleted in its entirety at any time. Simply contact us at privacy@LogicalMedia.com and provide the name of the service for which you provided information and let us know what level of opt-out you would like to exercise. These include: (1) Do not share information about me with business partners, (2) Do not solicit me with special offers other than those related to the service I signed up for, or (3) Remove my data from your database for such service completely. Once we receive this instruction, we will promptly take corrective action. Please note that we will need you to provide your email address or other previously provided personal identifier in order to identify you in the Data Opt-Out process. Also, please remember that if you choose to delete your information completely you will no longer receive the LOGICAL MEDIA service in question.

Access to Data

LOGICAL MEDIA allows consumers who have voluntarily provided personally identifiable data access to their data to ensure that it is correct and to make any changes. Please contact us at privacy@LogicalMedia.com.

MISCELLANEOUS  
Children's Privacy  
LOGICAL MEDIA is very sensitive to the issue of children's privacy. LOGICAL MEDIA websites, products, and services are neither developed for, nor directed at, children. If you believe your child has provided LOGICAL MEDIA with personally identifiable data, or registered at one of LOGICAL MEDIA websites, and you would like to have the data removed, please contact us at privacy@LogicalMedia.com. Changes to Our Privacy Policy

The issue of privacy is an evolving one. LOGICAL MEDIA is committed to the constant monitoring and examination of its privacy practices, and may, from time to time, institute changes to its Privacy Policy. In the event that any material changes are made to the company's privacy practices, we will promptly make changes to this privacy policy that discloses the changes.

CONTACTING US  
For more information, or if you have questions or concerns regarding LOGICAL MEDIA Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@LogicalMedia.com
